Hello I'm David Plaskett

406 GRANDE DRIVE, UNIT F MINOOKA, IL 60447 (630) 888-4250 dcplaskett@gmail.com

Skills

A high honor graduate in Information Technology with years of experience in project management, problem solving and technical skills. Eye for design and user experience, passion for technology and learning. Specializes in combining creativity and technical know-how to fulfill client's needs. Quick to learn new skills to shape to the needs of a project. Experience in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Python, and other technologies to build web applications.

Experience

AUGUST 2018 - PRESENT

Minooka Community Consolidated School District 201, Minooka- Technology Support Specialist

- Maintain the operating technology for an elementary school and school district.
- Plan, develop and maintain district webpage and mobile app using Finalsite CMS.
- Plan, develop and maintain the district-wide student link page.
- Implement SEO practices and maintain analytic information.
- Develop and expand district-wide social influence through content creation.
- Train teachers and staff in various technological systems.
- Diagnose and troubleshoot technical problems in software and hardware.
- Set up and maintain equipment for assemblies or other special events.
- Manage support with staff and parents through Jitbit ticketing system.
- Create and maintain documentation with Confluence.
- Systems used and supported:
 - o Windows, iOS, Chrome environments.
 - PowerSchool and Unified Classroom
 - o Finalsite CMS
 - Google Admin and Active Directory
 - Google Analytics and Search Console
 - Adobe Creative Cloud Suite
 - o FreePBX, Ruckus, Papercut, GLPI
 - o Clever, Seesaw, NWEA, aimsweb

AUGUST 2016 - AUGUST 2018

Freelance Web Designer, Minooka- Web Designer

- Design art assets and web templates.
- Create a plan system and development cycle.
- Use React, HTML, CSS, JS, jQuery, and Bootstrap to build interactions.
- Update web pages with latest portfolio content.
- Design and write blog entries, complete with new art and content.

MARCH 2005 - AUGUST 2017

Metal Erectors, Inc., Itasca- Journeyman Sheetmetal Worker

- Prepare work timelines.
- Report work progress and budget problems to clients and superiors.
- Interpret contract, technical information, and problems to clients and other professionals.
- Select, schedule, and coordinate activities with superiors, team members, and clients
- Respond to work delays, problem solving, and emergencies.
- Ensure safety, guidelines, and legal requirements are met.
- Train and mentor current and new employees.
- Work with deadlines to complete needed tasks.
- Communicate with other trades on timelines and work restrictions.

Education

AUGUST 2016 - SEPTEMBER 2018

University of Phoenix, Online- Bachelors of Science in Information Technology

Concentration in Advanced Multimedia Development

AUGUST 2017

freeCodeCamp, Online- Web development

Front-End Development Certification

MARCH 2014 - MAY 2016

University of Phoenix, Online- Associates of Arts in Information Technology

Concentration in Desktop Support